Privacy policy for Museum Explorer

* * *

A few of these web search services are provided by Museum Explorer and powered by Museum Explorer search partners.

This browser extension (hereinafter “Service” or “Extensions” or “Museum Explorer”) provides a platform that will customize your search-result page and your search provider. This page and "Museum Explorer" EULA/Terms of Service ("Terms") will show you terms of your use of these extensions.

#### Data we collect

We choose not to collect and/or use any of users information, but other search engines may receive information when users provide them.

If you search for something, other search engines may collect your country of origin, email address and, if you choose so, your nickname, telephone number, search history and title, website; but contrary to other search sites, we respect all our user’s privacy.

While you interact with the Extension we, as well as similar third-party vendors/service providers alike, may use technologies that could automatically or passively collect information about how the Extension is accessed and used (“Usage Information”). This information could include browser type, operating system, device type, page served, url visited, time, an estimation of your geographic location associated to your IP address and other information transmitted in http requests.

Usage Information is usually non-identifying, but to the extent Usage Information could be associated with you as a specific person (example: you could have registered for the Service) and provide us with personal information (like name, email, telephone number or home address), that will be treated as “Personal Information” and used only for purposes described in this Privacy Policy.

#### Personal User Data

The only occasion on which we may receive personally identifiable information about you is if you, the user, knowingly and willingly provide us with the information via email. This information is voluntarily submitted at your discretion, and is optional and normally required so as to allow us to reply to your email and correspondence. The network will never share with advertisers or other third parties the aggregate results of the data it receives.

#### Standard User Data

When logging onto the network, our servers will collect certain elements of standard information. Some of the data collected are: the amount of time you spend on various areas of the network or any related sites, the website from which you came, your browser type, any accessed information from the network and any downloaded pages. This type of information is commonly collected throughout most websites and will not impinge on your privacy. Infact these data will not identify you personally, unless otherwise stated. You are confirming, before reading or using any services of this network, that you understand the nature of data collection and our Privacy Policy. We and our network, will not retain, gather or disclose any standard data other than in collective user data forms.

#### Security

When we collect personal information directly from you, we follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our extension, you can contact us.

#### Cookies

At Museum Explorer, we don’t advocate in using cookies. In case our user changes settings, then our cookies are used to store those changes. But still, we do not store them or know how to trace you by them. As mentioned, we may use cookies in order to know how did you find us but with no relation to your search actions.

We also sampling part of the searches, but again, not in a personally identifiable way, as we do not store IP addresses or unique User ID.

#### Children

Our contents are safe for everyone. However if you are under the age of thirteen (13), we do request that you have the permission of your parents or your legal guardians to view any content within the network. This means we cannot and will not be held responsible for any information received or disclosed by our users.

#### Further Policies

We will not disclose personally identifiable information you may choose to submit to the network to any third parties. We follow a strict policy of no spam and no sales of personally identifiable information.

#### Disabling Cookies

Cookies can be disabled in your browsers settings. For detailed instructions on how to disable cookies using (amongst others) Mozilla, Netscape Navigator and Internet Explorer, visit: http://support.microsoft.com/kb/260971 , http://kb.mozillazine.org/Network.cookie.cookieBehavior

* * *
